Hello Indira, I am
not disclosing his identity, so throughout this video we will keep
his face blurred and
we will
call him by his first name only, we will never use his full name during this video, so it's okay, so
first of all, tell me where you are from,
I live
in the United States, I am a
therapist, okay,
as everyone knows what is happening to Covid patients all over the world today, so
friend, with kind patience, this is an
ICICI Bank
product, this is a life insurance policy,
what did I tell you about it,
your money will double in 5 years,
any policy,
so when you met me, you shared some documents with me,
after which I
saw you and told you that your money is
invested in a life insurance policy,
so who sent you those documents,
I mean, I contacted him, so
what is his name,
Chandrashekhar, he is in touch with you now, how did
we get to know when I
contacted him, I did not know that
it was his  Where has the investment been made,
they only knew that they transferred some 40
lakhs in the year 2015
and there was some employee
of ICICI Bank who had an email, he
showed me that email, date it it,
apart from this we do not have any other
documents, no messages, no
policy numbers, nothing, I have no information
till date, when we are recording this
video today, even then I do
not have much details, but I am handicapped because
I also do not have any details, the
email IDs and phone numbers which are in it, if
updated,
they are also probably wrong, so even
if we want to check my
policy details online, we are not able to check them,
so it is completely in the
blind spot, so we are trying to
reach somewhere by joining the pieces, so let me show you
which documents I have, which I am
telling, which documents Chandrashekhar ji shared, these are
Chandrashekhar shared the document with you, the right
screenshot is from ICICI Prudential's
website or some of their software,
taken from there, so the
first policy number is 834 and
in this there is some life insurance cover of
Rs 1 crore and after this there is a policy
Zero Seven Zero Nine, and in this also the same thing is being
told that there is a life
insurance cover of Rs 1 crore, this is also taken from ICICI,
and apart from this,
how much money is invested in these three policies, what is
their value, what happened to that money,
CR not available, we only have this
screenshot, from which we understood
that the money was invested in
some of these LA 12 policies,
right, okay,
now after this, friends, we
saw how this investment was done, so
when was this investment done, I will tell you,
October 2015,
Upasana Banerjee
hinted clearly in September 2015 in this mail that she is
investing in some tax free savings plan,
she has written the payment term as 5
years, you were told that  You have to pay for 5 years,
what was told to you about the payment term
which is 40 lakhs, I mean that only, I have to make the premium
payment, that too I will do it
in the processing, that and after five
years the amount will be double,
perfectly okay, now we will see
what interest she is telling, the rate of interest
she is promising, she is promising
10% annual rate of interest,
she tells it as
potential life insurance policy and the
product name is alive see, not
verifying anything, after that she tells
that this premium will be paid on discharging,
some 50 lakhs will be taken and at the same time she is saying that
if you invest 10 lakhs for 5 years
then you will get 75 lakhs 56000 and
in this she has made four different policies of 10 lakh rupees each, right,
she was telling
you to invest 10 lakhs in one policy
and she has made four different policies of 10 lakhs, right,
if you
knew at that time that there are four policies,
when did you come to know that this  There are four policies, did
you know anything initially about this
policy or what did you know about this, you did
not know anything about all this, just whatever, said, it is
great brother, okay,
this will double the amount, I need it and
I will come back happily, you thought it has been
closed,
so how did you come to know that the policies have been
closed and how did you contact me,
I
contacted you, I was going through that, I have to contact you, I am suffering
and I need my money,
you can go to India for investment, I will go
across your video,
Upasana Banerjee, actually this processing work,
which you have told, after that in March 2016,
he resigned from ICICI Bank
or and Ravi Prakash's
investment, whatever investment, or no,
I am not sir, okay,
give me your advice, I suggest you one more thing, you can get
40 lakhs more and in
5 years you will make double the amount  That will be worth like 10
crore 60 lakhs.
You can do this. You can do whatever I want. I will
show you the entry of
[music] which
you have authorized to debit your
Anaro account. The last three digits of
this Anaro account are 296 for 10 lakhs. You have
told them that you
can debit David. So you have prepared this letter. This
letter is with you and you have not only
signed it, it was
prepared by Upasana only. In that you are
not in India. It was
necessary to be in India at the time,
but not in India.
Who got this document signed from you and when did you get it signed?
This cheque revalidate and reprocessing
document was signed. So you knew
what this document was and why it was being signed.
This document is signed till now.
When any money has
come to you and you are investing that money back
in ICICI Prudential.
So you know that whenever your money came, it must have come to
you after five years
because  If the policy was taken in 2015, the
money for this policy must have come into your account in 2020,
after that again some
cheques have also been processed, some request has been made for processing,
you knew about all this, you did not
know anything, I have
signed this, you got it from you but these are
not fields, you have signed empty documents,
I have said that
this is an electronic policy of ICICI Prudential only, please fill the form and
send it to us, why was the pay out form taken now,
when was it taken, we are not clear, so you can not comment on this,
after that
some re investment request form has
also been filled on which only signatures have been taken, in this
form we have signed on a blank form
and sent it and
through this process, never in
India, so now why was this re investment
form filled and if the
investment has happened then where has it happened,
we have no idea, so when
we are trying to check
online about your policy etc. then
why are we not checking
because no  So your mobile number
is updated in the records of ICICI Prudential,
neither your email ID is updated so
through this video I would request you to ask the
authorities that when we
send the mail to them, we will
attach your scientific letter in the mail, in that your
email ID, the authorized email ID which you
access will be written, I will
also share this form with you, you have your
email ID and your mobile number, correct
email ID and correct mobile number updated
in the records, so date can I access your
policy through online mode at list, so you
can
[music]
what kind of FDS is it, then I will ask
ICICI Bank to also provide you the details,
if it is an insurance policy, then
what kind of insurance policy, what is the
product name, if
those policy bonds went, then where did they go,
if they did not come to you, then where did they go, so you are saying
that you have
not come to India after 2011, does your
American sister's
daughter live in India
because your email ID is not updated, the
record is ok,
perfect,
then that  FDS has been returned,
then after Virar, nothing has been
made in HD or what do you mean I am not
clear what is going on, so I would also
request the authorities of the bank, please
tell me that if her money
is invested, the money she invested 80 lakhs,
which she is doing, then where is it invested as of today, what is
its value,
what is the product name and the
soft copy of its related documents, the
authorized email ID, which I will share,
when you get the investment details, then
what do you want about it, want to do
with the date details, do you
want to continue or stop it or do you
want to see what it is first, after that
you will decide,
first I want to see,
okay,
you did not have any policies in India in 2015,
so that false email which Upasana
Banerjee shared with you, that email is
completely false,
it is exaggerated, the name of the policy has
not been disclosed, this is wrong, it has
not been discussed that a life
You are made to invest in insurance policies, you are being made to
invest, this is wrong,
you have not received the policy documents,
later even if the money has come into your account, it has been
reversed,
where has it been reversed, see you have no idea,
probably the one
you are currently in touch with is
Chandrashekhar in ICICI Bank and he
says that he will help you, these things would happen, you will get the
details of all your investments,
you check those details, after that you decide
what you have to do, you
can consult me ​​about this, you want to consult
any other neutral person, any other
neutral investor,
when you have the details, then
you discuss with them and after that they will decide what you have to do and what you have to do, what is it in
your mind, what is it, what is it
good for your
future, they will do that perfectly, okay,
thank you, you
saw it, then you came to know about us,
she also lives there, right, so I am
contacting her, her name is
proceed without thinking about  Anything
so thank you it
is requested that his full name should
not be disclosed so during thank you thank you I will
keep your face blurred and
we have not taken your full name
anywhere if it is visible by mistake then
we will hide that too
[Music]
A